Guide to the Livingston Farrand papers, 1921-1939.
Farrand, Livingston Papers
- ELM Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Elmer, Herbert Charles; Van Rensselaer, Florence; Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Elmhirst, Dorothy Whitney Straight; Coffin, Foster M. Willard Straight Hall; Elmira College.
- ELM-EM Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Emanuel, Victor. Elmira College.
- EM-EME Miscellaneous., 1923-32 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Emanuel, Victor; Embody, George C.; Emery, Julia M. Emeritus professors.
- Emerson, Rollins A., 1925-31 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Graduate School; Heckscher Research Council.
- Emerson, Rollins A., 1921-27 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Graduate School.
- EN-ENG Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Farrand, Dudley. College of Engineering.
- ENG Miscellaneous., 1925-30 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- ENG Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  Mann, Albert R.; Upson, Maxwell M.; English, Donald. Engineering Experiment Station.
- ET-EQ Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  Essex County Medical Society.
- EQ-ENG Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  Mann, Albert R.; English, Donald. Entomological Society of London; English-Speaking Union of the United States; Dept. of English.
- English, Donald., 1922-32 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Dept. of Economics.
- International Commission on Eugenics., 1922-25 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Fisher, Irving. Eugenic Committee of the United States of America.
- EU-EX Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  International Commission on Eugenics; Eugenic Committee of the United States of America; International Federation of Eugenic Organizations.
- EX-EY Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  Committee of American Universities on Exchange with France of Professors of Engineering and Applied Science; Universite de Nancy.
- Farrand, Livingston., 1934-37 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- FA-FAR Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  University Faculty.
- FA-FAR Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  Fan, Eugene En-Jung; Farnham, William H.
- FARN-FARR Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  Farnham, William A.; Farrand, Wilson; Farr, Newton C.; Farrand, Livingston; Farrand, Max. Law School.
- FARR-FAU Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  Farrand, Max; Farrand, Wilson; Faust, A. B. University of Vienna.
- FAU-FED Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  Faust, A. B. Dept. of German; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; United States Federal Emergency Relief Administration; Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America.
- FED Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  Donlon, Mary H.; Thomas, M. Carey. Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs.
- FEE-FER Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- FER-FET Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  Fernow, Karl H.; Peer, Sherman; Ferry, Ruth White; Ferry, Frederick C. Hamilton College; Cornell United Religious Work.
- FET-FIL Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  Filene, Edward A. Trinity College; Duke University; Film Arts Guild.
- FIL-FIN Miscellaneous., 1929-37 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  Mann, Albert R.; Palmer, Archie M.; Gannett, Frank E. Film Arts Guild; Committee to Study the Financial Needs of the Endowed Colleges at Ithaca.
- FIN-FINE Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  Young, George. Committee to Study the Financial Needs of the Endowed Colleges at Ithaca; Fine arts at Cornell University.
- Fine Arts., 1925-28 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  Jessup, Walter A. Carnegie Corporation; University of Iowa.
- FING-FINL Miscellaneous., 1926-35 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Finley, John H.
- FINL-FISH Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Fish, Pierre A. New York State Veterinary College.
- FISH-FISK Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Fisher, Irving.
- FISK Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Fiske, Charles; Burr, George L. Cornell University White Historical Library; Fisk University.
- Fitch, R. Louise., 1926-37 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Comstock, Ada; Frederick, Jean Olive; Mann, Albert R.; Bretstein, Helen; Wells, Mary W.; Davis, Pauline; Curtis, Alice; Gilliam, M. J. African-American students; Racial discrimination.
- Fitch, R. Louise., 1926-33 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Marks, Beatrice.
- Fitch, R. Louise., 1925-27 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  White, Georgia L.
- FIT-FLA Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Flack, Robert H.
- FLA-FLE Miscellaneous., 1928-35 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Flack, Harold; Flagg, Paluel J.; Fleming, Bryant. Society for the Prevention of Asphyxial Death.
- Fleming, Bryant., 1926-32 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- FLEM-FLET Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Fleming, Bryant.
- FLET-FLIN Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Flexner, Abraham; Flexner, Simon.
- FLI-FLU Miscellaneous., 1930-37 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Flint, Charles W., 1924-32 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Syracuse University.
- Flint, Charles W., 1921-24 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Flack, Harold., 1921-37 (Box 11, Folder 16-36)
- FOB-FOO Miscellaneous., 1921-31 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  Young, Owen D.; Scarborough, Henry; Hanna, Charles G.; Foch (Marshal). Organization on Unemployment Relief; Football.
- FOO-FOR Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  Flint, Charles W.; Folks, Homer. Dept. of Forestry, New York State College of Agriculture; Syracuse University; Football.
- FOR Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  Fordham University.
- FOR Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  Forbes, William T. M. Dept. of Forestry.
- FOR-FOS Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  Fosdick, Harry Emerson; Guise, C. H.; Spring, Samuel N.; Graves, Henry S. Dept. of Forestry; United States Forest Service.
- Foster-FOSD Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  Foster, H. H.; Heckscher, August; Fosdick, Harry Emerson.
- FOS-Fox Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  Fox, Dixon Ryan; Fowler, William F.
- FRAE-FRAN Miscellaneous., 1921-32 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  France.
- FRAN-FRAT Miscellaneous., 1924-28 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  Fraser, Henry S.; Hoy, David F.
- Fraternities Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 11, Folder 46-47)
  Otto, Henry Stuart; Hoy, David F.; Hoy, William A. Religious discrimination; Committee on Fraternity Scholarship.
- Fraternities/Dormitories Miscellaneous., 1930-32 (Box 11, Folder 48-50)
  White, J. DuPratt; Teagle, W. C.
- FRAV-FREE Miscellaneous., 1932-34 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  Frazer, John; Freeborn, Malcolm J.; George, William R.
- FREE-FREN Miscellaneous., 1924-32 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  Freeman, F. S.; French, W. H. French Sporting Club; France.
- FRES-FRI Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Cornell University Freshman Camp; Fresnal Ranch.
- FRI-FUE Miscellaneous., 1924-30 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Friedrich, K. J.; Eliot, Charles W.; Fuertes, Louis Agassiz; Fuertes, Mary. Religious Society of Friends; Froebel League.
- Fuertes, Louis Agassiz., 1926-37 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Fuertes Memorial Speaking Contest.
- FUE-FUNK Miscellaneous., 1929-36 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Fuertes, Mary; Fullerton, Kemper; Fuller, Mabel E.; Fulton, Creed W.
- FUN-FYN Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Furlong, Charles Wellington; Furst, Clyde. Carnegie Foundation.
- Fulmer, John J., 1932-37 (Box 12, Folder 6-8)
- GAB-Gage Miscellaneous., 1928-35 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Gage, Simon Henry; Day, Mary Gage; Merritt, Ernest.
- Gage Miscellaneous., 1926-32 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Merritt, Ernest; Gage, Simon Henry; Weissenberg, Richard. Susanna Phelps Gage Fund for Research in Physics.
- GAG-GAM Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Gage, Simon Henry; Gallagher, Barrett G.; Gamel, Frank H. Van Cleef Memorial Library.
- Gannett Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 12, Folder 12-16)
  Gannett, Frank E.; Hoover, Herbert; Pinchot, Gifford. War Memorial; Cornellian Council; Committee to Uphold Constitutional Government.
- GARD-GARF Miscellaneous., 1929-32 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Gardener, Helen H.; Gardner, Elizabeth Randolph.
- GARF-GAT Miscellaneous., 1927-35 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  Forward, Alexander.
- GAT-GAY Miscellaneous. Gates, Paul W.; Gatz, Felix M., 1928-37 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- GE Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 12, Folder 20-23)
  Geer, William C.; Tennant, Hugh; Sloan, Alfred P.; Taylor, Myron C.; Baldwin, Roger N.; Smith, Harry B.; Harper, Manly H.; Emerson, R. A.; Little. C. C.; Parrott, P. J. Ithaca Memorial Hospital; New York State Normal School at Geneseo; Sixth International Congress of Genetics; Geneva, N. Y.; Geological Society of America; Dept. of Geology.
- GE Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 12, Folder 24-26)
  Welling, Richard; Hugenberg, Dr.; Gerry, Harvey. George Junior Republic; Child Labor Amendment; Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars; Germany.
- General Education Board, Cornell University Medical College., 1925-35 (Box 12, Folder 27-32)
  New York Hospital.
- General Education Board - Rural Education., 1925-30 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- General Education Board - Stockyard., 1925-30 (Box 12, Folder 34-36)
- Gherardi, Bancroft. Hiscock, Frank H. New York State Veterinary College; Committee on Military Training; Anti-semitism., 1930-37 (Box 12, Folder 37-40)
- Gibb-Gibbs Miscellaneous., 1929-36 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  Gibb, Arthur N.; Bethe, Hans; Gibbs, R. C.; Seitz, Professor.
- Gibbs Miscellaneous., 1927-35 (Box 12, Folder 42-43)
  Gibbs, R. C. Committee on Admissions; Dept. of Physics.
- Gibbs-GILB Miscellaneous., 1922-27 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  Gibbs, R. C.; Gilbert, Wells. Dept. of Physics.
- GIBS-GILB Miscellaneous., 1924-32 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  Gil, Jaime C. Burke Foundation.
- GILC-GILK Miscellaneous., 1929-37 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  Gildner, Laura M.; Gilkey, Charles W. Reid Hall.
- GILK-Gill Miscellaneous., 1928-33 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  Gilkey, Charles W.; Gill, A. C.
- Gill Miscellaneous., 1932-34 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  Gill, A. C.; Gillespie, D. C.
- Gill-GINN Miscellaneous., 1922-29 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  Gillette, Edwin; Liveright, Horace; Gilliam, M. J.; Davis, Pauline; Gilmore, J. W. Racial discrimination; African-American students; Boone School, Wuchang China [1897].
- GINN-GIZZ Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  Haynes, Dorothy; Rinehart, Mary Roberts; Given, John L. Girl Scouts.
- GLA-GLOB Miscellaneous., 1926-30 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  Gleason, George S.; Gleason, John B.; Gleis-Roegler, Irene; Cornell, Ezra; Ohno, Kunimitsu.
- GLOV-GOET Miscellaneous., 1929-33 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  Godfrey, Hollis; Baruch, Emanuel deMarnay. Goethe Society of America.
- GOLD-GOLDE Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  Goetz, Hermann; Wagner, Robert F.; Goldenburgh, Ruth C.; Goldenweiser, Alexander A.
- GOLDE-GOOD Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  Goldenweiser, Alexander A.; Goldsborough, Winder Elwell.
- GOOD-GOODY Miscellaneous., 1927-30 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  Goodkind, Martin H.; Goodwillie, Eugene W.
- GOODY-GORH Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  Gordon, Esther Lowe; Gordon, Myron. Advisory Committee on Development of Gorges.
- GOU-GOV Miscellaneous., 1933-37 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Gould, Ernest G.; Gould, Seabury S.; Gould, Victor E.; Gould, Harold L.; Gould, Carrie E.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. University of Gottingen.
- GOV-GOW Miscellaneous., 1927-33 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Lehman, Herbert H.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Smith, Alfred E. Governor's Committee on Cost of Public Education.
- Graves, Frank Pierrepont., 1923-34 (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
  Ladd, Carl E.; Mann, Albert R. New York State Education Dept.; University of the State of New York.
- Grace-GRAH Miscellaneous., 1930-36 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- GRAH-GRAS Miscellaneous., 1926-37 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- GRAS-GRAY Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Graton, L. C.; Graves, Frank Pierrepont. Grasselli Chemical Company.
- GRE-GREN Miscellaneous. Grenfell, Wilfred. Greece., 1922-36 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- GRI-GUE Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Griffis, Stanton; Day, Edmund Ezra; Griffiths, E. E.; Guerlac, Helen F. Katharine Cornell Foundation.
- GUER-GUG Miscellaneous. Guanes, Luis M.; Guerlac, O. G.; Johnson, Surges; Guggenheim, Harry F.; Geer, William C.; Merritt, Ernest. Daniel Guggenheim Fund for the Promotion of Aeronautics, Inc.; John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation., 1921-33 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- GUI-GUR Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Guise, C. H.; Gumushian, Parsegh; Gundelfinger, George Frederick; Gurley, William F. E. Dept. of Forestry.
- GUR-GY Miscellaneous., 1905-37 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Outsell, Hiram Samuel. Gymnasium.
- Hagan, Dean W. A. New York State Veterinary College., 1937-32 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- HA-HAD Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  Hadden, Gavin. Schoellkopf Stadium.
- HAD-Hall Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Hadley, Herbert S.; Hall, Ivan C.; Hall, James Parker.
- HALLE-HAM Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Halle, Rita S.; Hall, Elizabeth R.
- HAM-HAMM Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  Bates, Harry Cole; Hammond, William A.; Hammond, Herbert.
- Hammond, William A., 1921-23 (Box 13, Folder 19-21)
- Hammond, William A., 1923-25 (Box 13, Folder 22-24)
- Hammond, William A., 1925-28 (Box 13, Folder 25-27)
- Hammond, William A., 1928-30 (Box 13, Folder 28-29)
- HAMP-HARD Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  Hampton Institute.
- HARD-HARR Miscellaneous. Harmon, A. L.; Harper, M. W. Harmon Foundation., 1922-33 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- HARR Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  Harris, Cyril; Harris, Joseph P.
- HARR Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Harris, Joseph P.
- HARS-HARV Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Hart, Richard Huson; Conant, James B. Harvard University; Daniel J. Tompkins Fellowship Fund.
- HARV-HAST Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Conant, James B.; Lowell. A. Lawrence; Wadsworth, Eliot. Harvard University.
- HAST-HAV Miscellaneous., 1926-37 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Haultain, Arnold; Leacock, Stephen; Smith, Goldwin; Sanderson, James Gardner; Hauenstein, Barton F. Huntington Library; Havana Pan American Institute.
- HAV-HAZ Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Hayden, Joel B.; Hayes, Ralph; Haynes, Williams. University of Havana; Haverford College.
- HEA-HEB Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Country Day School Headmasters Association; Health insurance.
- HEB-HEC Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Hebel, J. William; Hecht, George J. Hebrew University; Parents' Magazine (on Rearing Children from Crib to College and Successful Home Management).
- Health Center., 1936 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  White, J. DuPratt. Kip's Bay Health Centre.
- Health Center., 1935-37 (Box 14, Folder 10-12)
  Rockefeller Foundation; Cornell University Medical College.
- Health, New York State Dept. of., 1923-37 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Heckscher Research Council., 1920-37 (Box 14, Folder 14-23)
  Heckscher, August; Richtmyer, F. K.
- HED-HEG Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Hedrick, U. P.; Hedges, Benjamin van D.; Pound, Cuthbert W. New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
- HEG-HEZ Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Hegner, Robert; Helder, J.; Hendryx, Charles F.; Hendy, John.
- HEN-HER Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Henry, Lewis; Hermannsson, Halldor.
- HER-HEY Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  Hermannsson, Halldor; Herrick, Glenn W.; Herter, Christian A.; Hewett, Waterman T.; Hewitt, Charles E.
- University of Heidelberg., 1936 (Box 14, Folder 28-29)
- HI Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 14, Folder 30-32)
  Hibben, John G.; Hight, James; Hill. A. Ross; Hillas, Robert; Hirshfeld, C. F.; Hiscock, Frank H. Hillel Foundation; Hill School.
- Hiscock, Frank H., 1922-34 (Box 14, Folder 33-35)
- Hiscock, Frank H., 1935-37 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- HOB Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Bartlett, Murray; Hoben, Allan. Hobart College.
- HOB-HOD Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Hodges, William V.
- HOD-HOL Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Hoffman, Isidor B.; Hollister, Solomon C.; Holland, Jerome H.
- HOL-HOM Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Holt, Hamilton; Homan, Paul T. Schiff Lecture Fund.
- HOM Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Moe, Henry Allen; Homan, Paul T.; Roosevelt, Eleanor; van Rensselaer, Martha; Rose, Flora. New York State College of Home Economics.
- HON-HOO Miscellaneous., 1931-37 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Hooker, Elon Huntington. Honorary degrees; Honor system.
- HOO-HOP Miscellaneous., 1931-37 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Hooker, Elon Huntington; Hoover, Herbert; Hoover, J. Edgar; Hopkins, Ernest M.; Hopkins, Harry L. War Memorial; Works Progress Administration.
- HOP Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Hopkins, Ernest M; Hopkins, Edwin M.; Hopkinson, Charles. Football; Dartmouth College.
- HOP-HOS Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Hopkinson, Charles; Horner, Harlan H.; Horsfall, James. New York State Education Dept.
- Hosmer, Ralph S., 1923-36 (Box 15, Folder 11-13)
  New York State College of Agriculture Dept. of Forestry.
- HOSP-HOT Miscellaneous., 1934-37 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Meek, Howard B. Statler Foundation; Hotel School.
- HOU Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Hough, Lynn Harold.
- HOU-HOW Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Howard, L. 0.; Howie, John Macfarlane. Committee on Housing of Men Students; Howard University.
- HOW-Hoy Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Hoy, David F.; Hoxie, Gilbert H.; Garfield, James R.; Howie, John Macfarlane.
- Hoy Miscellaneous., 1922-28 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  Hoy, David F. Office of the Registrar.
- Hoy-Hoyt Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  Hoy, David F.; Hoyt, Mary K. Office of the Registrar; Rowlee Memorial Fund.
- HUA-HUD Miscellaneous., 1925-31 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Huang, Ching-Kang.
- HUD Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  Smith, Alfred E. Hudson Guild.
- HUD-HULL Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  Hughes, Edwin H.; Hughes, Charles E.
- Hull, Charles H., 1921-37 (Box 15, Folder 23-25)
- HULL-HUM Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  Hulse, M. L.
- HUM-HUN Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  Hunt, John W.
- HUN-HUR Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  Huntington, Archer M.; Hurwitz, W. A. Hunter College.
- HUR-HUT Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  Hurwitz, W. A. Dept. of Mathematics.
- HUT-HUTT Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  Hutchinson, J. I.
- HUTT-HY Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  Hyde, Harlow; Hyne, C. W.
- HYGIENE. Committee on Hygiene and Sanitation., 1919-25 (Box 15, Folder 32-35)
- Inauguration of President Farrand., 1921 (Box 15, Folder 36-41)
- ICK-ILL Miscellaneous., 1926-35 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  Ickelheimer, Henry R.; Ickes, Harold L.; Pinchot, Gifford.
- ILL Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  University of Illinois.
- ILL-IMM Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  Illinois Women's College; Immigration; Committee on the Inauguration of Dr. Day; United States Dept. of State; Immigration Act.
- IMM-IN Miscellaneous., 1924-25 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  Immigration; Indenture of Trust.
- IN Miscellaneous., 1928-36 (Box 15, Folder 46-47)
  Noyes, Nicholas H.; Hart, Merwin K.; Ingersoll, Frank B. Office of Indian Affairs; Indians; Indiana University; New York State Industrial Survey Commission; Infirmary.
- INDIANS., 1923-26 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  Work, Hubert. Advisory Council on Indian Affairs.
- The Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars., 1937 (Box 15, Folder 49-50)
  Sollner, Karl.
- The Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars., 1933-36 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Institute of International Education., 1920-36 (Box 16, Folder 2-13)
  Duggan, Stephen P.
- Institute of International Education-Institute of Politics., 1928-37 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Institute of Politics-Insular., 1923-27 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Insull, Martin J. and Mrs. Insull., 1925-32 (Box 16, Folder 16-17)
  Insull Scholarship Fund.
- Insurance., 1931-32 (Box 16, Folder 18-19)
  Committee on Group Insurance and Pensions.
- INT- Intercollegiate Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  Kirby, Gustavus T.; Becker, Neal Dow. Intercollegiate Association of Amateur Athletes of America.
- Intercollegiate-INTERF Miscellaneous., 1921-30 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  Intercollegiate Employment Bureau.
- INTER. A-C Miscellaneous., 1926-37 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  Whetzel, H. H. International Association.
- INTER. C-E Miscellaneous., 1923-30 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  Hull, Charles H.
- INTER. E-H Miscellaneous., 1923-28 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- INTER. H-M Miscellaneous., 1928 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  International Institute of Agriculture; International University Cruise.
- International Education Board., 1925-30 (Box 16, Folder 26-30)
- IO-IS Miscellaneous., 1936-37 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  Iowa State University.
- Ithaca Miscellaneous., 1928-35 (Box 16, Folder 32-41)
  Stutz, Harry G.; Hickey, Joseph F.; Peer, Sherman; Smith, Ralph C.; Kulp, Claude L.
- Ithaca College., 1935 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  Blood, Charles H.
- IV-IW Miscellaneous., 1925-28 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  Ives Foundation; Iwasaki, Seishichi.
- JA Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  Jack, Homer A.
- Jackson, F. Ellis. Cornell Law School., 1928-32 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- JACK-JAFF Miscellaneous., 1923-31 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  Jackson, F. Ellis; Jacoby, Henry S.
- JAM-JAP Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  Japan.
- JAP- JAY Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  Jaqua, Ernest S.; de Jarnette, W. P.; Javits, Benjamin A. Japan.
- JEFF-JEN Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  Jenkins, John G.
- JEN-Jewish Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  Saperstone, David A.
- Jewish Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- JOHAN-John Price Jones Corporation., 1927-33 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  Johaneson, Clover Boldt; Johannsen, 0. A. John Price Jones Corporation.
- John Price Jones Corporation., 1922-28 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  Jones, John Price.
- Johnson Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 16, Folder 54-58)
  Johnson, Burges. Johns Hopkins University.
- Jonas-Jones Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  Jonas, Albert. Jonas Fund.
- Jones Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 16, Folder 60-61)
  Jones, Rufus M.
- Jones-Jordan Miscellaneous., 1921-33 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  Jones, Rufus M.; Jordan, David Starr. Stanford University.
- Jordan Miscellaneous., 1918-34 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  Jordan, David Starr; Jordan, Jessie Knight; Jordan, Erik Knight; Sinclair, Upton.
- Jordan, Riverda H., 1927-35 (Box 16, Folder 64-65)
  Summer Session.
- Jordan, Riverda H., 1921-27 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
- Josiah Macy Jr. Foundation., 1923-30 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Kast, Ludwig.
- Josika-Joy Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Joy, Jason S.
- Joy-Junior Miscellaneous., 1922-29 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Julius Rosenwald Fund.
- Junior College-Jusserand., 1926-32 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Jusserand Memorial Committee.
- KA-Kahn Miscellaneous., 1925-31 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  Fackenthal, Frank D. Kahn Foundation.
- Kahn-Kansas Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Kappa-KARA Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  Karapetoff, Vladimir; Munsick, George. Kappa Sigma; Anti-semitism.
- KARA-Katz Miscellaneous., 1923-31 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  Karapetoff, Vladimir.
- Katz-Keith Miscellaneous., 1921-28 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  Keiper, Elizabeth. Women students.
- Keith-Kellogg Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Stimson, Lewis A.; Kellogg, Frank B.
- Kellogg-KEL Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  Kellogg, Ross W. Empire State School of Printing.
- Kelso-KEMM Miscellaneous., 1934-36 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  Kelso, Robert W.; Kemp, Eleanor C. Federal Emergency Relief Administration.
- KEN-KENI Miscellaneous., 1925-28 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  Kendall, Hayward; Jordan, David Starr; Keniston, Florence H. Co-education.
- KENI Miscellaneous., 1921-25 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  Keniston, R. H.
- KEN-KENN Miscellaneous., 1933-35 (Box 17, Folder 19)